## Ivan

# **Bryko**

## **Contact**

#### Location:

Ust-Kamenogorsk, Kazakhstan

#### **Email:**

ivanbryko@gmail.com

#### Skype:

Live:.cid.e07bcb612fe88d1b

#### **Skills:**

React & Redux

**React Native** 

Angular

Vue

Javascript

**HTML** 

**CSS** 

**SASS** 

Bootstrap

Node.js

Express.js

MongoDB

MySQL

Blockchain

Smart contract

NFT marketplace

## Summary

Senior Web Developer with over 8 years of React development experience. I can transform projects into great code and implement highly responsive UI components with the React concept also have enough experience with Angular, Vue. My focus is on web development and mobile development. I strive to write clean and usable code.

## **Skill Highlights**

- UI/UX design
- Clean code
- Complex problem solver
- Good communication
- API optimization

## **Experience**

Senior React Developer - 03/2020 to 09/2021

All Stars, LLC (.wrk), Novosibirsk, Russia

- Created mobile responsive custom components for an existing application.
- Worked on performance monitoring to improve app loading time.
- Wrote tests using Jest and reviewed the code of other developers.

#### Front-end Developer - 05/2014 to 07/2019

WebSailors, Taganrog, Russia

- Worked on providing API endpoints with Node.js/Inversify and MongoDB.
- Built from scratch admin platform for managing platform's database entities and users using React, Node.js, and Mongoose.
- Implemented complex UI components with React/TypeScript and SCSS.
- Improved the UX by creating several DnD-based components.
- Wrote scripts to use and manipulate data from various sources.

### **Education**

Master's Degree in **Computer Applications**-2014 Moscow State University , Moscow, 2009 - 2014